Hello friends, Namaskar, welcome to all of you once
again in today's
video. In today's video, we will
tell you that if the Tulsi card of ICICI
Lombard General Insurance Company is
lost, then how to
download it online. So friends,
for this, first of all, I have the phone number and
when the card will expire. Both these things are
very important. Without these, this decision cannot be taken. So
friends, let's start
how this will be done online. So
first of all, let's talk about ICICI Lombard
Test Board. I will also give you its link
in the description. You can open this link from there also.
So friends, on this subject, the
option Shankar's Register New UI
ICICI Lombard, you have to click on it
slowly. It opens, after that
I will login into it. Gmail will be used for everything
and it will be logged in from Facebook.
After logging in, it will open easily and
after it is on the desktop, it is written below.
Tap Tulsi. If we click on it, then
immediately select the policy number option here.
Number or phone number. So when Bigg Boss  Boss, the work will be done
and we can do it with this number also, so
I will put it with the policy number, I will put it
here on the polythene, I have first copied it,
you will put it here, I will
put it in trouble, the end policy
is that, when do I have to enter the expiry date, it will expire in
March or
later, I have to click on search, as soon as I
click on it, it will ask, I am
elected for taking this country, do you
want to deal with this flower, otherwise enter
this number of the same, if we were interested,
now we have to click on ok,
as soon as we use it, it will say, applicant is in
touch, okay, now it is fine, there is no
problem with the diseases, I will get to know
that I am in the process, you will get support, it is
loading, I have to go to
my God thing, Michael
C was done, after that this is shown,
this Tulsi, I have the tag, then
I have to take two spoons, the quantity,
I have tagged it, now this policy is so, let's do it in
Melbourne, only do it,
not after meeting, it will reach me, it will come on email in
20 minutes more  If you submit it after playing then you have the option to
come to Kochi,
Wagon R believed
one hour, in this the platform reaches here within 1 hour, so the
second option is to
get out of the view full and pause the piece of paper,
this is what he is saying, he might also be having some problem with his hair, that is why
you are not able to download it, so I will send the
mail to email and submit it, if
your email has been opened then
it will come to my voicemail,
we can also download it from Surma,
like if you print the idol, it does take
some time to get it,
it also takes an hour, then you can
send it again, you can send this to
Bargadwa town any number of times on mail,
this policy will come on mail,
thank you friends for watching the video,
if you liked the video then
please like, share and subscribe